bootbarn.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Boot Barn

Last updated 06/06/2018

Boot Barn corporate address: 15345 Barranca Parkway, Irvine, CA 92618

We value the trust you place in BootBarn.com, and we want you to be aware of the safeguards we have in place to respect your privacy. The below policy tells you about the information we gather about you and how we use it. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at custserv@bootbarn.com.

We also do not support SPAM. We are committed to sharing information and advertising promotions to our valued customers and we respect their privacy. Each of our email special promotions come with a simple "unsubscribe link" that permanently removes your address from our list.

### Types of personal information we may gather

BootBarn.com gathers personal information from you in order to provide superior service, communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you, customize our communications to you, administer our business, and improve your shopping experience. The following are examples of the personal information we gather from you.

  * **Purchases** – When you place an order, you give us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address plus payment information.
  * **Non-Purchases** – There may be instances when you are not making a purchase at BootBarn.com and you give us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address, and where applicable, payment information, or when somebody else gives us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address, and where applicable, payment information. Some situations when this may occur are when you return or exchange merchandise, receive a gift from BootBarn.com or enter a contest or participate in a promotion or survey sponsored by Boot Barn, Inc
  * **Personal Shopping Account** – If you create a Personal Shopping Account with us so that you may place orders more conveniently, you authorize us to store your name and shipping address(es)
  * **Catalog requests** – We need your name and address in order to mail you a catalog. We also require a phone number or e-mail address so that we can contact you in the unlikely event there is an error in your address or other delivery problem. To stop receiving catalogs, simply e-mail us at custserv@bootbarn.com
  * **E-mail updates** – When you subscribe to receive BootBarn.com e-mail updates featuring exclusive offers (like free shipping), product news, special discounts, contest announcements and more, we require your e-mail address. You can unsubscribe any time by updating your profile here.

### How we use cookies

We use cookies to help process your order through our website and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. To place an order and complete your transaction on BootBarn.com, you must have "cookies" enabled on your Web browser. (If you don' t want to enable cookies but would like to place an order, please call us toll free at 1.888.440.2668.

Cookies also help us:

  * determine which features and tools you use, and which pages you visit on bootbarn.com
  * remember which items you've placed in your shopping bag
  * enable you to checkout faster if you’ve created an account with us

We also contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partner, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our site.

If you have any concerns about leaving cookies on your computer for extended periods, you can delete them using your browser preferences or privacy menus.

### Our Email Program:

If you have agreed to receive marketing emails from us, you can opt out anytime by clicking the unsub link in the emails. We might still send emails to you about your transactions, accounts you have with us and any contests, sweepstakes you have entered. You may still receive marketing text messages if you have opted in to receive them. 

### Our SMS Program:

The mobile operators participating in this campaign are AT&T, Sprint, Virgin Mobile, T-Mobile (T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages), MetroPCS (GSM), U.S. Cellular, and Verizon Wireless. If your mobile operator is not participating, you will not receive a reply to your messages. Some operators may not support some services at the process offered. Pre-paid users may not be able to participate. Check with your mobile operator. Boot Barn collects certain information automatically upon subscription. Information collected includes the type of mobile device you use, unique device identifier and mobile operating system. To opt-in for Boot Barn mobile alerts and offers text JOIN to 20447 . By opting in, the Boot Barn mobile subscriber agrees to receive Boot Barn updates and offers via text. You agree to receive recurring mobile marketing text messages from Boot Barn to the mobile number provided by you. Consent is not a condition of purchase. The text messages are generated by an automated dialer from Boot Barn to the provided mobile number. Receive up to 10 messages a month. Reply STOP to 20447 cancel. Reply HELP to 20447 for help. Msg & Data Rates May Apply.

### Children's Privacy at Boot Barn 

Boot Barn® does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. Boot Barn®, Inc is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

### Use By Non-US Residents

The Site is operated in the United States under United States law. We do not intentionally offer goods and services to individuals outside of the United States. If you reside in another country, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be collected and stored in the United States or other countries that may have data privacy laws that are less protective than the laws where you reside.

### Updates 

Boot Barn® may find it necessary to update this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the revised Policy and the date of the last revision on our website so the consumer is aware of the changes.
